{
    "id": "c3ccd2653beb4f96a23e262db56f509d",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is the …………………….peak in the world.",
            "description": "The superlative indicates the highest degree.",
            "answers": [
                "highest",
                "higher",
                "high"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is …………………… than any other peak in the world.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "higher",
                "high",
                "highest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Sachin is …………………… famous than any other Indian cricketer.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Lead is …………………….. metal.",
            "description": "The article the is used before superlative adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "the heavy",
                "the heavier",
                "the heaviest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "No other metal is as …………………… as lead.",
            "description": "Positive adjectives are used in the construction as …as…",
            "answers": [
                "heavy",
                "heavier",
                "heaviest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mayank is …………………….. than any other boy in the class.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before the expression than.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant is ……………………… land animal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "big",
                "bigger",
                "biggest",
                "the biggest"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Preeti is …………………… girl in the class.",
            "description": "We use the superlative to compare one person or thing with the whole group to which that person or thing belongs.",
            "answers": [
                "prettier",
                "the prettier",
                "the prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Lotus is …………………….. than any other flower.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "more beautiful",
                "most beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You are no …………………….. than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "well",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Bhim was ……………………….. of the Pandavas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "strongest",
                "the stronger",
                "the strongest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The peacock is one of the ……………………. birds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more beautiful",
                "most beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}